Hello friends, once again you
are welcome to our channel Exam. If you
like the video then do not forget to like, share and
subscribe. And once again
friends, if you have not yet opened a demat account
for your Invested In,
then you will
find the link in the description of this video. Friends, we have
also made this Telegram channel clear for you. If
you want, you can join that too,
friends. That is also a free service. And one more
thing friends, if you do
not know all this trend analysis and you do
not like technical things, then you
will find that link in the description of this video,
friends, you can also watch it if you want. So
friends, Nifty is at an all-time high and is almost
running today. Today, it is an old time that
even within this, friends, there is a city which is still
getting the price of December 2019 and due to
technical reasons, there is a rise in this market, so friends, that is
why friends, I am talking about Allahabad General Insurance Company. It is a
large cap company, it is
not a small company, friends, its
market cap is around Rs. 100 crore and
its one year return is Rs. 8.1 crore.  If it is
more, then let's talk about what the company does,
friends. So, ICICI
Lombard General Insurance is India's best
private sector 9 life insurance company. If we
talk about its features, then the
error is zero, 552, 5162, six. So, there is
good news for those who have it. The score of March 18, 2000, will
also be credited to their account with a share dividend of Rs 4, friends. So,
let's talk
about this company, friends, let's
know a little news about this company,
with whom is this company currently tying up and
how is it performing. Recently,
friends, they have also tied up with Flipkart.
Now you can see that for a
week, such insurance to
consumer ICICI Lombard has tied up with them
and if we believe the broker's call,
friends, a target of Rs 1590 has been
given above the city. There is a target of Capital Bible
within this and friends, a few
months ago, ICICI Lombard General
Insurance also took over Bharti AXA Life
Insurance, so
you will see an increase in the results, friends.
This is the upcoming launch,
friends, let's go to its website and
try to understand it better. So
friends, ICICI Lombard's website has
over 40 million customers. They have faith in this because they are
providing services to 40 million customers.
Talking about their services,
friends, there are car insurance, two
new services, travel insurance, health
insurance, home insurance, cyber insurance.
And friends, if you talk further,
friends, friends, business insurance, most of them and
insurance renewal, all these things are
theirs. Friends, the faster the Indian economy
grows, the faster this insurance company will also
grow. Friends, tea, then
cyber insurance, travel insurance,
two-wheeler insurance, and four-wheeler
insurance, you can understand that there is still a
lot of growth left in it. So before
we move ahead in the video, friends, you can see this.
This is
also a part of my profile, my building. You
can take it if you want. Friends, this is a strange
city, it is
not very popular, but friends, it will keep
giving you fixed returns. Friends,
you can see in these areas that its
value is also zero.  164 If the market rises by 1%, the
stock will rise by 0.84%. If the
market falls by 1%, that topic will rise only by
0.5%. So, 20180 is a stock.
From the monthly chart, you can see
how its growth has been over the past several years.
Friends, this was around 2017. Handloom was launched in
this city and friends, you
can see how its preparation has been since then.
Friends, this is just the beginning, the picture is still very much
left. Friends, this is the
only company in the private sector which
currently does this insurance. The other two
companies are government companies which are currently
listed on the NSC. Friends,
you can see on the daily chart,
friends, you are getting this from the December price.
Currently, it is 149,528. You can expect further growth within this.
And secondly, friends,
if you talk about its support,
its first support is of Rs. 1450
and its second support is of
Rs. 13,100.  Friends, it has very
strong support. Friends, if we
talk about its target, then its first
target is ₹17,100. And if we
talk about the long-term, then
friends, it depends on you above ₹2000.
That will be visible within one to two years. So let's
talk about the reason for that.
Friends, its RSI is currently of Chiffon. The
results that came in it in the month of February, in the end of
January, then friends, there was a
buying opportunity for it, then it went below ₹30. This meant that the
shoulder had passed. If
you did not buy, then friends, there is
still an opportunity to buy in it.
Similarly, friends, MSD also, friends, you
can see that it is giving Total Police Gurdaspur and
you can buy it if you want. So,
friends, let's see how it traded on NSE.
Last day, friends,
its opening
price on AC was of 1466 and the half that was
placed on it was of 1501. Its
closing price was of 1455 and  The
quantity was above 1495, if we talk about the delivery then
friends seven were middle aged and if we
talk about the delivery quantity forces in percentage then friends the delivery was 59%,
this is not from any buysale ad, friends
this video is to educate you,
friends I hope you will like this video,
we will meet again in our next
video, thank you for watching.